그 여자가 너에게 반하지 않은
유일한 여배우란 말야?
You're telling me
this actress person...
...is the only woman you ever wanted
who didn't want you back?
그래! 잠깐
Oh, my God.
거기엔 너도 포함되지?
Is this what it's like to be you?
많이 좋아하나 봐?
-You're crazy about her, huh?
-You have no idea.
상상도 못할 거야
함께 무대에 서면
키스하고 안고 싶어져
When we're on stage, I get to
kiss her and touch her.
감독과 집에 가는 모습을
보고 있으면
She goes home with the director...
...and it's like somebody's
ripping out my heart.
내 맘이 찢어진다구
그런 심정을 안다니
정말 잘됐어
Oh, it's so great to see you
feeling like this.
- 안녕
- 어서 와
아버지 전화를 받았는데...
Dad called this morning.
실비아 이모가 돌아가셨대
Aunt Sylvia passed away.
정말! 정말! 좋다!
다들 흥분에 떨고 있어
We were all
pretty shaken up about it.
뭔가 잘못된 거 아냐?
죽음이란 건 슬픈 일이잖아
Am I missing something?
I thought death was supposed
to be sad, in a way.
실비아 이모가 그리
좋은 분이 아니었어
Well, Aunt Sylvia was...
... not a nice person.
냉정하고, 괴팍한 분이었지
She was a cruel, cranky old bitch.
돌아가신 건 안 됐어
And I'm sorry she died.
- 아빠가 인형 집은 보내셨대?
- 곧 도착한대
Did Dad say I get the dollhouse?
-You get the dollhouse.
-I get the dollhouse!
나도 인형 집을 갖는다!
인형이 살 집?
멋지다
A house for dolls!
That is so cool.
난 어릴 적에,
통이 있었어
When I was a kid, I had a barrel.
인형을 통에 넣었어?
You had a barrel for a dollhouse?
그냥 통만 있었어
No, just a barrel.
인형 집이 오면
우리 같이 놀아
You know what? You can play
with my dollhouse.
정말? 정말?
Really?
언제든지
Any time you want.
어릴 적 소원이 인형 집을
갖는 거였어
When I was young I wanted
to play with this dollhouse.
물론, 지금은 감상용이지
갖고 놀 생각은 없어
But no! It was to be looked at,
never played with.
우리 할머니도 똑같은
말씀을 하셨지
My grandmother said
the same thing to me.
The One With the Doll House
- 나 왔어, 소피
- 왔어
안녕하세요?
점심 잘 먹었어
Thanks for lunch.
You didn't have to walk me here.
여기까지 바래다 줄
필요는 없는데
괜찮아, 그냥 온 거야
That's okay. No problem.
사무실에 여자 란제리를
걸어놓진 않아
You realize we don't keep
the women's lingerie here.
응, 지금 봤어
Yes, I realize that.
- 여름 카탈로그야
- 바로 이거야
-Summer catalog.
-That's the stuff.
베르사체 송장이 어딨지?
Rachel, I need the Versace invoice.
안녕하세요?
직원은 아니시죠?
You don't work for me.
과장님
제 친구 챈들러 빙이에요
Joanna, this is my friend
Chandler Bing. Joanna.
조애너 과장님
빙?
재밌는 이름이군요
Bing? That's a great name.
It's Gaelic for,
"Thy turkey's done."
게일족 말로
'너의 칠면조가 다 됐다'래요
이제 갈게요
반가웠습니다
-I'm gonna go. Nice meeting you.
-You too.
- 저두요
- 잘 가, 챈들러
사람이 원래 저래?
So what's wrong with him?
원래 좀 맹해 보이지만
저는 이제 거의 모르겠어요
Nothing. He's just goofy like that.
I actually hardly notice it anymore.
아니, 좋단 뜻이야
I mean, is he married
or involved with anyone?
혹시 기혼자거나
애인이 있나?
아뇨, 미혼이고
애인도 없어요
He's not married or involved
with anyone.
레이첼... 있잖아
아냐, 됐어
Actually, you know what?
Forget it.
- 원하시면 제가 물어볼게요
- 그럴래?
-I'll ask him for you, if you want.
-Would you?
그래도 너무 몸 달은 것처럼
하지마, 소피처럼 말이야
Or is it too sad and desperate,
like something Sophie would do?
저 여기 있어요
-I am here.
-I know that.
알아
이것 봐!
Look at it!
벽지가 좀 어둡지만...
괜찮아
Wallpaper's a little faded.
That's okay.
카페트가 좀 낡았네
Carpet's a little loose.
바닥이 나무야!
Hardwood floors?!
- 안녕
- 왔니?
모니카!
너무 아름답다
-It's so beautiful!
-I know!
그래!
- 내가 준비해왔어
- 좋아
So I'm here, ready to play!
이 집을 위해서 준비했어
어디 보자
I brought a bunch of stuff
for the house, so check it out.
이게 뭐야?
What's this?
개야, 집마다 개가 있잖아
That's a dog.
Every house should have a dog.
지붕에다 오줌싸라구?
Not one that can pee on the roof.
방사성 폐기물 위에 세워진
집이라 변종이 된 거야
Maybe it's so big because the house
was built on radioactive waste.
집이 재채기도 하니?
And is this in case the house sneezes?
아냐,
그건 다락방의 유령이야
No, that's the ghost for the attic.
난 유령 싫어
-I don't want a ghost.
-Well, nobody wants a ghost.
유령은 누구나 싫어해
그래도 이 집엔 있어
But you've got one...
이 집이 고대 인디안 묘지
자리에 지어졌거든
... because the house is sitting on
an ancient lndian burial ground.
이 집이 방사성 폐기물과
고대 인디안 묘지에 있는 거야?
Wait a minute. The house
was built on radioactive waste...
...and an ancient
lndian burial ground?
그건 말도 안 돼
That would never happen.
넌 미국 정부가 어떤지 몰라
Obviously you don't know much
about the U.S. government.
- 안녕
우리 얘기 좀 해
-I need to talk to you.
-Sure. What's up?
그래, 뭔데?
미안, 챈들러에게 한 말이야
Oh, sorry. I meant Chandler.
알고 있어
I know.
그래도 혹시나...
Well, if something comes up....
너희가 덜 어색한
단계로 접어든 걸 축하해
I'm glad you guys are past
that little awkward phase.
조애너 과장 알지?
My boss. Joanna. When you left...
네가 나가자마자
너에 대해서 묻더라
...she started asking questions
about you....
잠깐 본 건데?
Liked what she saw?
내 행동은 어떻대?
Dug my action, did she?
챈챈맨의 위력을 보시라!
Checking out the Chan Chan Man!
너무...
That was...
초현실적이다
...surreal.
어때?
관심 있니?
What do you think?
Are you interested?
응, 괜찮아 보이더라
매력도 있고, 나야 좋지
She seemed cool. Attractive.
I'll do it.
고마워, 잘됐다
과장님한테 잘 보일 거야
Thank you, Chandler.
This is great. She's gonna love me.
공룡의 공격이다!
모두 집안으로 들어가!
Dinosaur attack!
Quick, everybody into the house!
피비, 됐어
그만 하자
All right, Phoebe, you know what?
That's it. That's it.
공룡도, 유령도
거인 개도 됐어
No dinosaurs, no ghosts,
no giant dogs, okay?
크기도 안 맞고,
빅토리아풍과 안 어울려
They're not the right size, they're
not Victorian and they don't go.
알았어, 됐어
Fine.
가자, 공룡아
Come, dinosaur. We're not welcome
in the house of no imagination.
상상력이 없는 집은
우리도 필요 없어
피비, 전문가 입장에서
말하는 건데....
While we're on the subject,
I have to say that dinosaurs...
공룡과는 손 붙잡고
가지마
...they don't go, "ruff!"
작은 건 괜찮아
The little ones do.
- 케이트
- 좋은 아침!
-Hey, Kate.
-Morning.
지난주에 말해준
그 식당에 갔었어요
I went to that restaurant
you talked about
귀염둥이! 이리 와요
얘기 좀 합시다
Hey, lovely.
Come, talk to me for a minute.
식사했죠, 맛있었어요
생선요리였죠, 좋았어요
I ate the food. It was good.
I had the fish.
안녕하세요
로렌이에요
케이트 보조 대역이죠
I'm Lauren. Kate's understudy.
조이 트리비아니예요
Joey Tribbiani.
알아요, 당신 팬이에요
I know.
I'm a big fan of yours.
네?
What?
라모레이 박사를 보느라고
수업 시간도 바꾸고 그랬죠
I used to schedule my classes
so I could watch Dr. Drake Ramoray...
...on Days of our Lives.
'우리의 날들'이요
-Get out of here. Really?
-Absolutely.
- 정말이에요?
- 물론이죠
But then they dropped you
down that elevator shaft.
그런데 엘리베이터에 끼어
죽게 한 건 너무했어요
아주 설득력 있는 죽음이죠
They gave me the shaft, all right.
어머, 너무 재밌네요
You're so funny.
리허설 끝나고 뭐 하세요?
술이라도 한잔 하실래요?
What are you doing after rehearsal?
You want to get a drink?
그게...
좋아요, 술 한잔
좋죠
Sure. A drink sounds great.
좋아요
-Cool. I'll see you then.
-All right.
- 그럼 있다 봬요
- 그래요
이제 연기를 해봅시다
All right. It's time to act,
my talking props.
한번 떠들어봐요!
- 안녕
이것 봐라
내 인형 집이야
Look everybody!
Look at my new dollhouse!
봐, 봐!
Look, look!
이게 뭐야?
Hey, what's this?
미끄럼 계단이야, 봐
It's a slide instead of stairs.
Look.
아주 재밌다, 피비
Very interesting, Phoebe.
이건 뭐야?
What's this?
약초 방이야
먹을 수 있는 가구지
The licorice room.
You can eat all the furniture.
손님이 오면
접는 침대를 펴면 돼
And when guests come over, they can
stay on the Tootsie Roll-away bed.
지금까지 본 것 중에
최고다!
This is the coolest house ever!
아로마 방에 가고 싶은 사람?
Does anyone want to join me
in the Aroma Room?
- 저요
-All right.
-I would.
여길 봐, 내 장식장 봤어?
Hey, guys? Guys!
Did you see my new china cabinet?
이거 봐!
Watch. Watch.
이것도!
And? And?
우리 아빠 집도 저랬어
Hey, my father's house does that.
좋아! 어땠는지 말해봐
How did it go?
Tell me everything!
영화 좋았고, 식사 좋았고
쌀쌀한 뉴욕의 밤 분위기 좋고!
The movie was great...
...dinner was great, and there's nothing
like a cool, crisp New York evening.
근데 난 그걸 즐길 수 없었어
조애너 같은 여자는 처음이다
Of course, I didn't enjoy any of that
because Joanna's such a dull dud!
챈들러, 너무 좋아!
Chandler is fantastic!
네?
-What?
-You know how people just click?
우린 천생연분이야
그게 어떤지 알지?
그가 날 데리러 옴과 동시에
내가 문을 열었어
He came by to pick me up, I opened
the door and it was just like, "click!"
- 그런 말 안 해?
- 저는...
Did he tell you?
게다가 너무 착해
정말 착하지 않아?
Doesn't he have a good heart?
- 저는...
- 그래, 너무 좋은 사람이야
And he's so sweet. He said he'd
call, so put him straight through.
전화한다고 했으니까
바로 바꿔 줘
-lsn't this great?
-Don't spoil it.
- 정말 잘 됐네요
- 기분 깨지마
여보, 제발 가지마
안 떠날 거지?
Come on, baby, don't go. Please?
What do you say?
여보세요? 당신이군
잠깐만
It's you.
Just one sec.
전화를 받고 올테니까
I'm going to take this call.
그때는 이 극장 무대에
매혹적인 게 보이길 바래요
When I continue,
I hope there will appear on-stage...
...this magical thing
that in the theater we call...
순간에 전념해요!
...committing to the moment!
괴상하지 않아요?
The guy's like a cartoon.
당신은 못 느껴요?
What do you see in him, anyway?
좋을 때도 있잖아요
He happens to be brilliant.
당신이 데이트하는
저 스웨터 보단 낫죠
Which is more than I can say
for that sweater you're dating.
난 스웨터엔 관심 없어요
I'm not interested in her sweater.
스웨터 속이 중요하죠
It's what's underneath her sweater
that counts.
언제부터 남의 데이트
상대에 신경을 썼죠?
And besides...
...since when do you care
who I'm with?
난 신경 안 써요
신경 써주길 원해요?
I don't care.
Why, do you want me to care?
신경 써주길 원하길 원해요?
Do you want me to want you to care?
당신은요?
Do you?
뭐요?
What?
이렇게 말하긴 두렵지만,
하던 거 계속합시다
Okay. I'm afraid to say this,
but let's pick up where we left off.
여보, 제발 가지마
안 떠날 거지?
Come on, baby, don't go. Please?
What do you say?
있어야 할 이유가 없어요
I've got no reason to stay.
그만! 그만해!
제발 그만해!
Stop!
Stop it! You must stop!
당신들 연기는 끔찍스러워
You are bad actors!
각본도 끔찍해!
This is a terrible play!
내일 아침에 봅시다
I'll see you in the morning.
1주일 밖에 안 남았어요
I can't believe we go on
in a week.
할 수 있을 거예요
Hey, it's gonna be all right.
오늘 일찍 끝났으니까
머그컵 색칠하러 갈래요?
Since we're getting off early,
do you want to go paint mugs?
네?
What?
어제 말씀 드린 곳이요
At the place I told you about
last night?
그래요,
컵에 색칠하는 곳이요
Yeah, with the mug-painting.
아주 잘 기억하죠?
I was so listening to that.
근데 오늘은 남아서
연습해야겠어요
But you know what?
I need to work on my stuff tonight.
알았어요
내일 만나요
I'll see you tomorrow.
그래요
먼저 갈게요
괜찮아요?
Are you okay?
네, 괜찮아요
I guess.
이 장면을 어떻게 하죠?
What are we gonna do about the scene?
모르겠어요
I don't know.
좀 더 극적인 게 필요해요
Maybe if it had more heat.
어쩌면 되죠?
Well, how do you mean?
아내는 남을 이유를
찾고 싶어하죠
Adrianne's looking for a reason
to stay, right?
남편은 키스도 못해요
Victor can't just kiss her.
He's gotta...
그는 아내에게 이유를
찾아줘야 돼요
... he's gotta give her a reason.
찐한 키스는 어떨까요?
Maybe he could slip her the tongue.
아니면... 여자를 잡고
Or maybe...
... maybe he could grab her
and lift her up.
번쩍 들어올려요
좋아요, 그럼 아내가
다리로 남편의 허리를 감죠
Then Adrianne could wrap her legs
around his waist.
남편의 옷을 찢고
그의 가슴에 입을 맞추죠
Then she could rip off his shirt and
kiss his chest and stomach.
남편은 입으로 아내의
드레스를 벗겨요
Then he could use his teeth
to undo her dress and...
그리고 콱 깨물죠!
...and bite her!
네, 결국...
거칠고 동물적인...
Then right when the scene ends,
he could take her...
...with this raw, animal....
이렇게요?
Something like that?
That's pretty much
what I had in mind.
내 생각과 거의 비슷해요
네
- 왔냐?
- 안녕
아침부터 술 마셨니?
It's a little early to be drinking.
아니
결국 케이트와 일을 냈다
Things finally happened with Kate.
- 정말? 잘 됐다
- 그래
You're kidding? That's great.
너무 놀라웠어
사랑을 나눈 뒤에...
It was so amazing.
After the lovemaking...
Oh, my.
세상에
몇 시간 동안
자는 모습을 지켜봤어
... I just watched her sleep for hours.
숨을 들이쉬고, 내쉬고...
Just breathing in...
...and breathing out.
꿈을 꾸고 있었나봐
눈이 이렇게 움직였거든
I knew she was dreaming because...
... her eyes kept going like this.
조애너와 안 맞아
내가 한 말이라곤...
I'm telling you,
she's got it all wrong.
All I said was, "This was fun.
Let's do it again sometime.
"재밌네요, 또 옵시다
전화할게요"
I'll give you a call."
이런! 그래서 전화 올 거라는
말을 했구나?
I wonder why she thinks you're going
to call her?
데이트 끝엔 누구나 하잖아
It's what you say at the end
of a date.
반가웠어요, 잘 가요
그랬어야지
You can't just say,
"Nice to meet you. Good night?"
그 얼굴에 대고?
To her face?
헤어질 때쯤, 뭔가를
기다리는 듯한 분위기에
I'm standing there...
...she's waiting for me to say
I'll call her...
'전화할게요'가 저절로
튀어나오더라
...and it comes out.
I can't help it.
어쩔 수 없었어
강박을 느낄 정도였어
It's a compulsion.
남자가 전화한단 말이
꼭 한다는 건 아니잖아
When a guy says he'll call,
it doesn't mean he's going to call.
넌 그런 적 없어?
This never happened to you?
난 늘 받았어
Well, they always called.
잘났어
Bite me.
전화 왔어?
-Did he call?
-No, sorry.
아뇨, 죄송해요
왜? 한다고 해놓고
왜 전화를 안 하는 거야?
Why? He said he'd call.
Why hasn't he called?
Maybe he's intimidated by smart,
strong, successful women.
똑똑하고, 강하고, 성공한
여자 기피증이 있나봐요
소피, 말참견 좀 하지 마
Sophie, will you please
climb out of my butt.
- 전화를 왜 안 한 대?
- 그게, 아마도...
Why hasn't he called, Rachel? Why?
제 상관이라는 게
부담스러웠나봐요
Maybe he feels awkward because
you're my boss.
- 부담? 무슨 부담을 느껴?
- 그게...
Awkward? Why should he feel awkward?
부담스러운 건 레이첼 아냐?
그래서 전화하지 말랬지?
You didn't tell him
not to call me, did you?
아뇨!
직장 상사와 친구의 데이트가
불편하면 방법을 찾아봐야지
If you're uncomfortable with
your friend dating me...
...there are always ways to fix that.
전화해, 당장!
Call her. Call her now!
한 마리 매처럼 채가네
Multiple so many paper cuts.
왜 전화 안 하지?
왜? 왜?
"Why hasn't he called, Rachel?
Why, why? I don't understand!"
이해할 수 없어, 왜?
한다고 했는데, 왜지?
I'm telling you, she's flipped out!
She's gone crazy!
과장이 잔뜩 골이 나있어!
화가 났다구!
- 그럼 전화기 줘
- 지금 웃을 기분 아냐
Well, give me the phone then.
She thinks it's my fault
you haven't called her.
과장은 내 책임이라고
생각하니까, 빨리 해
You have to call her.
막무가내로 부탁 아닌 명령을
하는 사람의 말을 들으라구?
You can't call somebody
after this long to say:
"In case you didn't notice,
I don't like you."
아님, 같이 외출이라도 해
Then you'll have to
take her out again.
싫어!
정말 지루한 여자야
She's really dull,
and she gets this...
속눈썹에 마스카라
덩어리도 묻히고 다녀
...gross mascara-goop thing
in the corner of her eye!
상관없어! 상관없어!
I don't care!
한번 더 데이트하고서
진짜 확실하게 끝내버려
You'll take her out again
and end it...
...in a way she knows it's ended.
아무리 어쩔 수 없다해도
절대로 전화한단 말 하지마
I don't care how hard it is.
Don't tell her you'll call her again!
좋아, 알았어
All right, fine!
이번은 점심 데이트야
1시간 이상은 못해
But just lunch.
From now on, I get my own dates.
이제 내 짝은 내가 찾아
절대로 여자 소개하지마
I don't want you setting me up again!
그거 좋지!
That's fine!
- 우리 소리 좀 크지 않니?
- 알아
-That's just a lot of big talk.
-I know.
모니카?
샤워 중이야
I'm in the shower!
불이야! 불이야!
Fire! There's a fire! Fire!
- 안녕
로렌과 얘길 했는데,
우리 사이를 밝혔어요
I talked to Lauren.
I told her how things were with us.
당신은 감독한테 말했어요?
Did you talk to Marshall?
무슨 얘기요?
About what?
지난 밤 얘기요
About what happened with us.
아뇨
그 사람이 알아야 할
이유가 없어요
No, there's really no reason
why he should find out.
별 일 아니었잖아요
So let's not make a big deal
out of it, okay?
그게 무슨 뜻이죠?
그건 별 일이에요
What are you talking about?
It was a big deal.
You can't tell me last night
didn't mean something to you.
지난밤 일이 별 거 아니란
말은 말아요
분명 일어난 일이고, 당신도
그리 훌륭한 배우는 아니죠
I was there.
You're not that good an actress.
그건... 순간적으로
일어난 거였어요
I was just caught up in the moment.
That's all it was.
그뿐이에요
기분 나빴다면 미안해요
Joey, I'm sorry you feel bad, but...
자고 나서, 그것의 의미가
다른 적도 있지 않아요?
... haven't you slept with a woman
and it meant more to her than to you?
아뇨
- 안녕, 케이트
- 안녕, 로렌
안녕, 로렌
나쁜 놈!
Hi, pig!
- 놀래켜서 미안해
- 괜찮아
Sorry I scared you in there.
It's okay.
아무튼, 난 샤워기를
손보고 있었어
By the way...
... I was just checking
the shower massager.
알아
안녕
직장에 전화했었어
집에 불이 났어
I tried to reach you at work.
There's been a fire.
뭐?
어머... 맙소사!
What?
Oh, my God!
어떻게 된 거야?
What happened?
화재가 발생한 곳은
여깁니다
We believe it originated here...
아로마 룸이죠
...in the Aroma Room.
대피는 잘 했어?
Did everyone get out okay?
기린은 괜찮고,
해적도 괜찮아
The giraffe's okay,
and so is the pirate.
이게 뭐니?
-What's this?
-No, don't look!
피비, 안돼
그거 안 보는 게 나을걸!
You don't want to see
what's under there!
입양한 인형인데!
The foster puppets!
괜찮아요, 그냥 보여서요
자꾸 보이거든요
It's not a big deal. It's right
here, and it's all the time.
점심 잘 먹었어요
Thanks again for lunch.
저도 즐거웠습니다
-This was pleasant.
-lt was, wasn't it?
그렇죠?
- 음식도 맛있었죠
- 그렇죠?
-The food there was great.
-Wasn't it?
그럼, 잘 있어요
So take care.
당신도요
You too.
즐거웠고, 전화 드리죠
언제 또 봅시다
I'll give you a call.
We should do it again!
좋아요, 기다리죠
Great. I'm looking forward to it.
- 레이첼, 전화 메모는?
- 소피 책상에요
-Any messages?
-Sophie's desk.
챈들러! 전화할 거야?
Are you gonna call her?
- 아니
- 챈들러?
미안해, 나약하고
덜 떨어져서 미안해
I'm sorry, okay? I'm weak
and pathetic and sorry.
솔직히 말해, 지금 하라구
You are gonna tell her.
You'll tell her now.
저... 전화 안할래요
I'm not gonna call you.
What?
네?
죄송해요
I'm sorry.
생각도 없이 한다고 해서
죄송해요
I'm sorry I said I was going to
when I'm not.
당신이 문제가 있어서가
아니고, 레이첼 잘못도 아니죠
This has nothing to do with you.
And this isn't Rachel's fault.
It's me.
제가 여자에 있어서
심각한 문제가 있어요
I have serious problems
when it comes to women.
책임감이나 친밀감에
문제가 있고...
I have issues with commitment,
intimacy...
마스카라 덩어리도요
... mascara goop.
I'm really sorry. It's just that...
정말 죄송하지만
계속 만날 수가 없어요
...this isn't going to work out.
이런 식으로 끝나는 건 싫지만
솔직하게 말해주니 고맙군요
This isn't how I was hoping
this would end...
... but I guess I have to appreciate
your honesty.
네... 그래요
그럼...
즐거웠고, 전화 드리죠
언제 또 봅시다
I'll give you a call.
We should do it again sometime!
어쨌든, 베스
Anyway, Beth,
what I'm saying is...
너희 집에 갔을 때
네 기분을 몰랐단 거야
... I should have considered your
feelings before I went home with you.
내가 요즘 여자들 입장이
돼보는 중이거든, 미안해
I've recently learned what it's like
to be on your side...
...and I'm sorry.
날 용서할 수 있겠어?
Do you think you can forgive me?
그래, 고마워
그럼 잘 있어
Great. Thanks.
제니퍼?
Hello, Jennifer?
로리오 부인!
제니퍼 있어요?
Hi, Mrs. Laurio.
Is Jennifer there?
나갔군요?
She's not home, huh?
사실, 부인께도 드릴
말씀이 있어요
Actually I kind of need
to talk to you too.